

CONTACT

+91-9723771828 gautamanshulga7@gmail.com

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019 Bachelor of Mechhanical

Gandhinagar Institute Of Technology

2014- 2015 Higher Secondary School

Kendriya Vidyalaya Ahmedabad

LANGUAGE

English, Hindi, Gujarati

SKILLS

Strategy Management
Business Development
Good Hands on CRM
Google Analytics
Communication

ANSHUL GAUTAM CLUSTER REVENUE HEAD

ABOUT ME

I consider myself to be very an extroverted, meticulous and skilled at establishing and upholding business relationships. I promise to use my skills gained from my education and personal experience and to bring a strong sense of dedication, motivation and responsibility to this business

WORK EXPERIENCE

BYJUS (CLUSTER REVENUE HEAD) FEB 2023- PRESENT

- Develop and implement sales strategies and tactics to achieve revenue targets within the assigned territory.
- Conduct regular performance evaluations, set targets, and provide constructive feedback to drive continuous improvement.
- Monitor sales activities, track performance metrics, and provide accurate sales forecasts and reports to the senior management team
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams such as marketing, product development, and operations to ensure alignment and maximize sales effectiveness.
- Participate in industry events, trade shows, and conferences to enhance brand visibility and generate leads.

BYJUS (BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT MANAGER) FEB 2022- JAN 2023

- Created reports and presentations detailing business development activities
 - Coordinated innovative strategies to accomplish marketing objectives
- Collaborated with sales and marketing departments to support project rollout.

Handled a team of 16, driving 8 crore + revenue in 12 months.

ANSHUL GAUTAM CLUSTER REVENUE HEAD

WORK EXPERIENCE

BYJUS (BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATE) JULY 2020 - FEB 2022

- Boosted revenue by bringing in and cementing relationships with new clients and optimizing servicing of existing customer accounts.
- Generated record of 5.5 Lakh + Revenue in one week in direct sales.
- Delivered 95 lakh+ revenue within period of 13 months.
- Was responsible for growth of 3 associates through trainings as team captain for 3 months during the tenure.
- Maintained extensive knowledge of company products and services to provide top-notch expertise to customers.

ADIDEV SYSTEM (BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATE APRIL 2019 - MARCH 2020

- Competent in team management, revenue management, marketing, B2C, customer relationship management, and operations management.
- This is an individual contributor position in a high performance, employee-oriented atmosphere that places a premium on offering distinctive automotive parts.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Scintillating Performer of the Month for September 2022. Outstanding Mentor Award at Byjus.
- Recognizing exceptional management performance at the Gujarat level.